Jared Ethan D. Limjoco

Manila, Philippines | +63 917 633 0409 | limjocojared9@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Github

CAREER SUMMARY

A BS Computer Science graduate with a major in Software Technology. He has experience with Java, Python, and JavaScript. His background includes work in web development, software development, and AI/ML, focusing on creating practical solutions to real-world problems.

EDUCATION

De La Salle University

Manila, PH

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science - Major in Software Technology

2020 - 2024

• CGPA: 3.600, Magna Cum Laude

WORK EXPERIENCE

Yondu, Inc.

Manila, PH

Junior Software Engineer Intern

June - August 2023

- Worked with 8 Junior Software Engineers to develop the company's Knowledge Base project, a centralized platform for collecting, organizing, storing, retrieving, and distributing knowledge among the organization's 500+ employees.
- Assisted in debugging and resolving over 20 software issues, contributing to the overall stability and reliability of the Knowledge Base application.
- Used React.js and Tailwind CSS for front-end development, focusing on creating the user and role functionality for the application.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Enhancing Urban Planning Through Remote Sensing for Monitoring Sidewalk Accessibility Challenges Faced by Abled Individuals Undergraduate Thesis

2023 - 2024

- Collected heart rate and first-person video data and analyzed it using YOLOv8m to assess sidewalk accessibility.
- Atlas, a custom crowdsourcing platform, was modified to fit the study. The database is hosted on MongoDB and deployed via Vercel.
- Implemented an XGBoost Regression Model to calculate accessibility scores based on collected data features from data collection.

CO-CURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

La Salle Computer Society

Manila, PH

2022 - 2024

Associate Vice President for Socio Civic

- Spearheaded five (5) Socio Civic projects, such as the Computer Literacy Program (CLiP), where speakers were invited to discuss subjects promoting Computer Literacy to the selected beneficiaries.
- Collaborated with external organizations to ensure the success of the committee's projects.
- Helped organize 12 Socio Civic projects, which focus on assisting the mental wellness of the 900+ members of the organization.

Junior Officer for Corporate Relations

2021 - 2022

- Prepared and implemented the projects under the committee such as Tech Talk and Tech Careers.
- Provided updates and reports to his assigned Associate Vice President for Corporate Relations regarding projects and sponsors.

Computer Studies Government

Manila, PH

2023 - 2024

Director for Internal Relations

- Oversaw the operations of the college government's Internal Relations Committee.
- Responsible for overseeing the execution of four (4) projects led by the committee.
- Handled the organization's email system, handling over 180 emails per month, and successfully negotiated over 50 partnerships, significantly expanding the organization's network.
- Connected the college government to over 20 possible partners within the university for the organization's events such as CCSJourney, a platform that provides CCS students with career-related opportunities and academic tips.

DLSU Computer Batch 2024

Manila, PH

Chairperson for External Relations

2021 - 2022

- Part of the pioneering officers who established the organizational framework and operations for his batch student government.
- Co-chaired the operations and welfare of the External Relations Committee and its four (4) members.
- Improved the committee's templates and processes, enhancing the committee's functions and optimizing its system.
- Ensures seamless operation of the organization's email system, processing over 100 emails monthly and successfully negotiating over 100 partnerships, reaching out to over 20 potential collaborators and more than 8 speakers for the organization's annual events.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Technologies: Java | Python | JavaScript | TypeScript | C | React.js | Next.js | Vue.js | Tailwind CSS | SQL | MongoDB

Skills: Figma | Canva | paint.net | Adobe Photoshop | Google Suite | MS Office | English Language | Filipino Language

Soft Skills: Adaptability | Advocacy Building | Community Development | Critical Thinker | Detail Oriented | Leadership | Problem Solving | Project Management | Resilient | Resourceful